<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on </title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 00:18:12 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Regex&#39;s: A quick little cheatsheet</title>
      <link>/posts/regex_cheatsheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/regex_cheatsheet/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s not frequent I come across a need for a regex - perhaps to my own detriment - but when I do, I often find myself forgetting what specific parts may mean. Here&amp;rsquo;s a little cheatsheet I made myself ~ perhaps there&amp;rsquo;s some value for you.
   Symbol Name Meaning     . Wildcard Anything can take this guy&amp;rsquo;s place. You&amp;rsquo;ll need to escape (\.) it for periods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up a Raspberry Pi - Headless</title>
      <link>/posts/raspberry_pi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/raspberry_pi/</guid>
      <description>This one is more or less straight to the point. We&amp;rsquo;re going to setup a fresh raspberry pi in a headless state. It&amp;rsquo;s fairly easy if you keep your wits about you. Unfortunately you&amp;rsquo;ll need either a keyboard/mouse + monitor or an ethernet connection to your device in order to get the wifi step of these instructions done.
Raspbian Lite &amp;amp; Wifi Connect  Download the image from raspberrypi Burn to the SD card (straight from the ZIP) with the free Etcher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Setup ZSH</title>
      <link>/posts/setting_up_zsh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/setting_up_zsh/</guid>
      <description>One of the things I love to do is tinker - to an almost unhealthy degree. Having not been satisfied with the autocompletion bash provides, and curious what alternative shells had to offer, I found ZSH. In this guide, I&amp;rsquo;m going to walk you through how I setup ZSH on my Windows machine (inside WSL) - but the instructions compare similarly for my Mac.
First Step, ZSH You&amp;rsquo;ll want to boot up your terminal / WSL terminal and install the ZSH package.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Profiling in NodeJS with Environment Variables</title>
      <link>/posts/nodejs_profiling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nodejs_profiling/</guid>
      <description>While standing up a REST API for a work project, I spent a lot of time editing the IP, port, and other parameters within my server as I swapped from production and development environments. After being fed up with the constant back and forth, I searched for a better solution. In this tidbit, I&amp;rsquo;m going to present my solution.
Reading Environment Variables in Node An easy solution would be to simply pass environment variables when launching NodeJS, pulling the configuration from inside our files to the commandline during launch time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>